reachli.com 2015-03-18

# Reachli

PRIVACY POLICY

Reachli recognizes the importance of protecting the personal information that it holds. This policy outlines Reachli's policies and procedures regarding its collection, use, retention and disclosure of such personal information.

In the course of its business activities and, in particular, in facilitating Members' access to the Reachli Site and Reachli Services, Reachli collects personal information about its Members.

**Defined Terms**. Several of the important terms used in this Privacy Policy, including "Member", "Reachli", "Reachli Services", "Reachli Site", and "Vendor" are defined in Reachli's "General Terms of Use for Members and Vendors".

**Personal Information Only** : Reachli's privacy principles apply only to personal information about identifiable individuals. They do not apply to business information, such as the name, title, business address or telephone number of an owner or employee of an organization.

**Why Reachli Collects Personal Information:** Reachli primarily collects personal information to permit communication with Members regarding the Reachli Site and Reachli Services.

Reachli may also collect personal information for purposes related but secondary to our primary purposes, for example, to process credit card payments or to collect unpaid accounts, to advise clients about new products or services, to advise clients and others of special events or available opportunities, and to review delivery of the Reachli Site and Reachli Services to maintain quality control.

We use your personally identifiable information: (a) to send you information regarding Reachli Services and your subscription to the Services; (b) to track your compliance with the Reachli "General Terms of Use for Members and Vendors"; and/or (c) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. 

You agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Services and request for information regarding additional Reachli products and/or services.

**How We Collect Personal Information:** Reachli only collects personal information by lawful means, and only that which is reasonably necessary for the stated purposes. In almost all cases, and whenever possible, we collect personal information about Members directly from Members.

**How We Use Personal Information:**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and e-mail address (where possible). 

We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. ****

Reachli may use personal information to: provide access to the Reachli Site and Reachli Services; manage and develop Reachli's business and operations; learn about the needs of current and potential Members; develop or offer services and products tailored to these needs and communicate with these clients regarding current and future Services; respond to and follow up on Visitor and Member inquiries, comments and suggestions; address financial matters including billing and record-keeping for audit and account collection purposes; and report illegal, unethical or other serious and unacceptable misconduct on the part of Members.

**Disclosure of Personal Information** : Under normal circumstances, **** Reachli will only disclose personal information for purposes related to the provision of one or more Reachli Services to a Member, or with the express consent of such Member, or if required or authorized by law. If Reachli or its assets were to be sold, the prospective purchaser would normally conduct a "due diligence" review of Reachli's records. This could involve a review of Reachli's files, including personal information. Any such review would be subject to strict confidentiality provisions and would not permit the recording or removal of any personal information.

**Consent to Collection, Use and Disclosure:** We may obtain a person's consent to the collection, use and disclosure of his or her information either expressly, for stated purposes (such as in a Membership application or a request for information about the Reachli Site and Reachli Services), or implicitly, such as when the purposes are indicated by the relevant circumstances. Any such consent may be withdrawn or amended by contacting Reachli's privacy staff ([privacy@Reachli.com](mailto:privacy@Reachli.com)) and subject to any legal or contractual restrictions and upon reasonable notice to Reachli. For example, if a person tells us that he or she no longer wishes to receive information about the Reachli Site and Reachli Services, we will comply with said request.

A person's consent to Reachli's collection of certain personal information may be required for Reachli to provide the Reachli Site and Reachli Services. However, Reachli will not require, as a condition of providing access to the Reachli Site or Reachli Services, that any personal information unrelated to Reachli be collected.

**Reachli Partners and Sponsors:** Some Reachli Services are offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with a non-affiliated partner or sponsor. To provide Visitors and Members some of these Reachli Services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. Reachli will share non-identifying and aggregate information, but not personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered. 

**Responses to Email Inquiries:** When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to Reachli, the return email address is used to respond. Reachli does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not store or share the return email address with any third party.

**Voluntary Member Surveys** : We may conduct both business and individual Member surveys. We encourage Members to participate in these surveys as they provide us with information that enables us to improve Reachli Services and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our Member surveys is always voluntary. 

We take the information we receive from Members responding to Member Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it to create broader, general responses to the survey questions (data such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of current Reachli Services and new ones. This aggregated information may be shared with third parties. 

**Special Cases** : In exceptional circumstances, Reachli may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Reachli Services or Reachli Site, if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to obey laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Use or other policies; to operate the Reachli Services properly; or to protect Reachli and our Members and Vendors.

**Use of "Cookies"** : A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on the hard drive of a person who visits a Website such as the Reachli Site. Reachli may use cookies to collect, store, and track information for statistical purposes to improve the Reachli Services and to manage our networks. If you are a Member, we will use a cookie to save your settings and provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your Member information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit websites that are linked to the Reachli Site, you may be required to accept cookies. Non-affiliated partners or sponsors may also use cookies. Reachli does not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaims responsibility for information collected through them. 

**No Privacy Here:** Member acknowledges that in general, other than personal information provided to Reachli to set up a Reachli account, all messages, comments, questions and other information and communications submitted or posted by a Member to any part of the Reachli Site (collectively, "Communications"), presently or in the future, such as message boards, discussion groups, blogs and other communications facilities available to Members or Vendors (collectively, "Communities"), are public and not private Communications, and that others may access and read such Communications without the knowledge or consent of Member. If any of the Communities permits the submission of Communications on a confidential basis, that fact will be stated on the web page for such Communities.

**Retention and Destruction of Personal Information** : It is expected that some Members will enjoy the Reachli Site and Reachli Services over a period of months or years, and it can be useful not only for Reachli but also for such Member that their personal information is to be kept on file. Reachli therefore may retain a person's Member's personal information for up to five years after their last contact with Reachli. This ensures that Reachli is able to answer questions about the Reachli Site and Reachli Services previously provided.

Inactive Member files will be destroyed after five years, unless Reachli receives a request to destroy them earlier. Paper files containing personal information will generally be destroyed by shredding. Electronic information will be deleted from electronic files (server logs and databases) where it is stored, and, when the hardware is discarded, Reachli will ensure that the hard drive is physically destroyed.

**Updating, Correcting, or Deleting Information:** Since Reachli uses a Member's personal information to provide him or her with access to the Reachli Site and Reachli Services, it is important that such information be accurate and complete. If any of your personal information changes or you would like to delete your account, please inform us so that we can make any necessary changes. Simply send your request via e-mail to: [team@Reachli.com](mailto:team@Reachli.com).

We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Security of Personal Information:** Reachli uses appropriate security measures to protect against loss, theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, use or modification of personal information. Such measures will vary depending on the sensitivity, amount, format, nature and storage of the personal information and will involve, as applicable, physical, organizational and electronic security measures, including premises security, restricted file access to personal information, technological safeguards including security software and firewalls to prevent unauthorized computer access, and password and security policies. Members should be aware that Reachli cannot ensure the security of personal information transmitted by regular email, which is not a fully secure medium. Reachli requires that Vendors and third party service providers to whom personal information may be transferred provide a level of security for such personal information that meets standards established by Reachli. 

**Access to Personal Information:** We will respond promptly to any request for access to your personal information. There will be no cost for reasonable requests to such access, unless you request copies of records or your request involves significant retrieval costs. We will advise you of the cost, if any, prior to retrieving such records or information. Reachli will not respond to requests for access to personal information that are frivolous, vexatious or repetitious. 

In certain circumstances, we may be unable to provide access to some or all of the personal information that we hold about you. Such circumstances include those in which the personal information cannot be separated from the records of others, or cannot be disclosed for reasons of personal security or commercial confidentiality.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:** As part of our regular review of all of our policies and procedures, we may revise our privacy policy from time to time and may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us [privacy@Reachli.com](mailto:privacy@Reachli.com).

**Reachli's Website:** The Reachli Site may contain links to other websites, which are not governed by our privacy policy. On the Reachli Site, as with most other commercial websites, we may monitor traffic patterns, site usage and related site information in order to optimize our web service. We may provide aggregated information to third parties, but these statistics do not include any identifiable personal information.

**Questions, Concerns, Requests for Access:** If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, wish to access your personal information, or wish to change your preferences regarding our use of your information, please contact us at: [privacy@Reachli.com](mailto:privacy@Reachli.com).

Reachli, Inc.  
Phone: (888) 600-4430  
Email: [privacy@Reachli.com](mailto:privacy@Reachli.com)
